[
      { "answer": "d'abord", "question": "zunächst" },
      { "answer": "après", "question": "dann/dannach" },
      { "answer": "ensuite", "question": "schließlich" },
      { "answer": "et puis", "question": "und dann" },
      { "answer": "enfin", "question": "als Letztes/schließlich" },
      { "answer": "parfois", "question": "manchmal" },
      { "answer": "une semaine sur deux", "question": "jede zweite Woche" },
      { "answer": "le jeudi", "question": "Donnerstag" },
      { "answer": "souvent", "question": "alt" },
      { "answer": "toujours", "question": "immer" },
      { "answer": "depuis", "question": "seit" },
      { "answer": "tôt", "question": "früh" },
      { "answer": "tard", "question": "spät" },
      { "answer": "de ... à", "question": "von ... bis" },
      { "answer": "pendant", "question": "während" },
      { "answer": "avant", "question": "vor" },
      { "answer": "quand", "question": "wann" },
      { "answer": "hier", "question": "gestern" },
      { "answer": "maintenant", "question": "jetzt" },
      { "answer": "aujourd'hui", "question": "heute" },
      { "answer": "demain", "question": "morgen" },
      { "answer": "bientôt", "question": "bald" }
]   